Okay, cool. So we've deployed our contract,
OK 酷，我们已经部署好了合约
we've automatically programmatically verified our contract.
并且使用自动化程序验证了我们的合约
What's next? Well, what did we do last time,
下一步是什么？好吧，我们上次做了什么？
we started interacting with the contract.
上一次是要开始与合约进行交互了
So let's do const. Current Value equals await simple storage dot retrieve.
所以我们要执行 "const currentValue = await simpleStorage.retrieve()"
To get the current value,
以此来获取当前值
simple storage, that's all. We have a retrieve function, which returns the favorite number,
"SimpleStorage.sol" 中，有一个 "retrieve" 函数，返回的是 "favoriteNumber"
so let's get the current value.
所以让我们来获取当前值
And we'll do console dot log,
要做的就是 "console.log()"
the current value is and then some string interpolation, current value.
"Current Value is:" 后面是一些字符串插值 "currentValue"
And then we'll go ahead and update the current value
接下来要做的是更新当前值
by doing cons. Transaction response equals await simple storage, that store
做法是 "const transactionResponse = await simpleStorage.store()"
will store the number seven, and then we'll await transaction response dot Wait,
我们要存储的值是 7，然后是 "await transactionResponse.wait()"
we'll wait one block for that transaction to go through.
我们将等待一个区块以确保交易被确认
And we'll grab the updated value by saying const updated value equals await simple storage dot retrieve.
获取更新值的方法是 "const updatedValue = await simpleStorage.retrieve()"
Then we'll do console log.
接着就是 "console.log()"
The added value is updated value.
"Updated Value is: $"
Awesome. And this is going to be our whole script.
很好，这就是我们完整的脚本了
So if I can zoom out for a little bit, I know it will be a little bit small here,
我可以把视角放大一点，我知道这样窗口可能会有些小
we've got this huge main function, which does what?
我们现在有了一个巨大的 main 函数，它做了什么
Well it deploys our contract. If we're on a test net, it then verifies our contract.
它部署了我们的合约，如果是在测试网上，它还会验证我们的合约
And then it updates the value to seven.
接着它把值更新为 7
And we have our verify function down here.
我们在这里还有一个 "verify" 函数
And we have a section of our code that calls our main function.
并且还有一部分调用 main 函数的代码
Now for run this on the hard hat network.
现在我们要在 "Hardhat network" 上运行一下它
What do you think will happen? Well, let's try
你觉得会发生什么？好，让我们来试一下
yarn, or net run scripts. Deploy dot j s.
"yarn hardhat run scripts/deploy.js"
Alright, awesome, we get exactly what we saw before
非常好，我们得到了和之前完全一样的结果
we get deploying contract deployed contract to
我们得到了 "Deploying contract" 还有 "Deployed contract to"
current value is zero, update value seven.
"Current Value" 是 0, "Updated Value" 是 7
And there's nothing in here about verification. That's exactly what we want.
并且这里没有任何关于验证的信息，这正是我们想要看到的
Now, moment of truth. Let's try this on Rinkeby.
现在，关键时刻来了，让我们在 Rinkeby 上试一下
We'll do yarn, RT hat run scripts, deploy dot j s, dash dash network Rinkeby.
我们要运行 "yarn hardhat run scripts/deploy.js --network rinkeby"
And it's gonna go a lot slower, because obviously now we're deploying to an actual test net,
这个过程会比较慢，因为我们正在部署到一个真正的测试网上
where the blocks actually need to be mined.
那里要有实际的区块被挖出来
And we see we haven't deployed the contract. Now that our contract is deployed.
可以看到我们确实已经部署了合约，现在我们的合约已经部署好了
We know that we're currently waiting six block confirmations for us to go ahead and verify.
目前我们需要等待六个区块确认才能进行验证
And actually I should add console dot log,
其实我应该添加一段 "console.log()"
waiting for block the x's
"Waiting for block txes..."
so that we don't get campus weird. Oh, wait, what are we doing now?
这样我们就不会感到诸如 “哦等等，我们现在在干什么?” 这种困惑